<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>TeslaTunes</title>
        <link>https://tattwamasi.github.io/TeslaTunes/app/appcast.xml</link>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>Version 1.2.3</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
            <div class="markdown-body">
                        <ul>
                            <li>Added a new option <code>Embed multivolume disc # into track #</code>.  This option will change the track number for tracks on the 2nd and subsequent volumes of multivolume sets to be the volume number * 100 + the track number.  This is useful when the album name is the same for each volume in the set, and all the tracks from all the volumes are getting displayed together.  Without this option, you'd have a bunch of track 1s, then a bunch of track 2s, etc. in some situations.  See issue <a href="https://github.com/tattwamasi/TeslaTunes/issues/4" class="issue-link js-issue-link" data-id="75930162" data-error-text="Failed to load issue title" data-permission-text="Issue title is private" title="Playlist order is weird, and lists unexpected playlists">#4</a>
                            </li>
                            <li>Fixed the playlist ordering... sort of.  See issue <a href="https://github.com/tattwamasi/TeslaTunes/issues/7" class="issue-link js-issue-link" data-url="https://github.com/tattwamasi/TeslaTunes/issues/7" data-id="127570189" data-error-text="Failed to load issue title" data-permission-text="Issue title is private">#7</a>
                            </li>
                            <li>Updated the Sparkle autoupdate component and update URLs to address <a href="https://github.com/sparkle-project/Sparkle/issues/722" class="issue-link js-issue-link" data-id="129913968" data-error-text="Failed to load issue title" data-permission-text="Issue title is private" title="MITM Security Mitigations (VulnSec)">sparkle-project/Sparkle#722</a>
                            </li>
                            <li>Updated the app to allow updates on OS X 10.11+.  See <a href="https://github.com/sparkle-project/Sparkle/issues/644" class="issue-link js-issue-link" data-url="https://github.com/sparkle-project/Sparkle/issues/644" data-id="108920780" data-error-text="Failed to load issue title" data-permission-text="Issue title is private">sparkle-project/Sparkle#644</a>
                            </li>
                            <li>Updated taglib component.</li>
                        </ul>
                              </div>
                              ]]>
                          </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 05:16:12 -0800</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/tattwamasi/TeslaTunes/releases/download/1.2.3/TeslaTunes_1.2.3.zip"
                sparkle:version="1.2.3"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                length="3558544"
                />
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Version 1.2.1</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <p><strong>New options for <em>"Remap album artist->artist, etc."</em> and <em>"Strip tags for playlists"</em></strong></p>
                
                <p>By request added two options to help workaround limitations in the Model S media player.</p>
                
                <ul>
                <li><strong>"Remap album artist->artist, etc."</strong> is a new option to help prevent cases where an album which contains multiple artists, but a single album artist, would get split into multiple album listings under the Model S play by album view.  By remapping the album artist to the artist tag, the Model S will show all the songs under the same album again.  In order to not lose the artist tag info, it is appended to the song title</li>
                <li><strong>"Strip tags in playlists"</strong> will cause the app to remove the title, album, artist, and (if the <strong>"Set genre to playlist name"</strong> option is not selected) the genre tags from all songs in the destination playlists.  This might help with duplicate entries getting listed when using the Model S play by album, song, or artist views, at the expense of not having the tags displaying when playing the songs through the playlists, whether via the genre map option or via folder.  Note that currently the Model S doesn't display the tags via the play by folder view anyway, so not really losing anything in that case.</li>
                </ul>
                
                
                <p>These options default to off, but will remember their settings just like the other options.</p>
                
                <p>This release also fixes a couple bugs including some Apple Lossless to FLAC tag issues and a playlist sync bug that would affect first time syncs of a playlist.</p>
            ]]>
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 02:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/tattwamasi/TeslaTunes/releases/download/1.2.1/TeslaTunes_1.2.1.zip"
                sparkle:version="1.2.1"
                type="application/octet-stream"
                length="3354177"
                />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
